To account for class imbalance during training of a binary classifier,
对于二元分类器训练过程中出现的类别不平衡性问题
LinearLearner offers the hyperparameter, positive_example_weight_mult.
LinearLearner 提供了超参数 positive_example_weight_mult
This is the weight assigned to
它表示在训练二元分类器时
positive or fraudulent examples when training a binary classifier.
分配给正样本或欺诈性样本的权重
The weight of negative examples or valid data is fixed at 1.
负样本或有效数据的权重固定为 1
From the hyperparameter documentation, it reads,
该超参数的文档中指出
"If you want the algorithm to choose a weight so
“如果你希望算法选择一个权重
that errors in classifying negative versus
使分类负样本与正样本的误差
positive examples have equal impact on training loss, specify balanced."
对训练损失的影响一样 则指定 balanced”
So in this cell, I've defined a balanced estimator as
我在这个单元格中像之前一样定义了平衡 estimator
usual with the same number of epochs and recall tuning parameters.
周期数和召回率优化参数与之前的一样
I've added just one more hyperparameter,
不过还添加了一个超参数
setting positive_example_weight_mult to balanced.
将 positive_example_weight_mult 设为 balanced
Then as usual, I'm training the balanced estimator and deploying it,
然后像之前一样 训练并部署平衡 estimator
creating a balanced predictor.
创建一个平衡预测器
Then I'm running my evaluation code as before,
然后像之前一样运行评估代码
passing in my balanced predictor,
传入平衡预测器
my test features, and test labels.
测试特征和测试标签
In this case, I can see a high recall and a higher precision than last time.
可以看到召回率很高 并且精确率比上次高
In fact, if we look at the metrics from last time,
实际上 看看上次的指标后
we can see that we misclassified over 3,000
会发现我们将超过 3,000 个有效样本
valid examples as fraudulent and had a very low precision.
错误地分类成了欺诈性样本 所以精确率很低
In this balanced example,
在这个平衡示例中
we've reduced that number of misclassifications by at least a factor of 3.
我们将分类错误的样本数至少减少了 3 倍
So now I'm done evaluating this tuned and balanced model,
评估完这个优化过及平衡过的模型后
and I'm going to delete the endpoint.
删除端点
Now one thing to note is that we're training with
注意 我们在训练时
a fixed recall value of 0.9 or 90 percent,
将召回率固定成了 0.9 即 90%
but this value may vary when it's actually applied to test data as seen here.
但是当模型应用到测试数据上后 这个值可能会变化
In real-world tasks, you'll often be given
在实际任务中 经常你需要
unbalanced streaming data and a specific metric to define the success of a product.
使用不平衡的流式数据 并根据特定指标判断模型的性能
So knowing how to tune a model for a specific metric
所以 知道如何根据特定指标优化模型
and balance the class weight for training is a really valuable skill.
并为训练模型平衡类别权重是很重要的技能
In fact, next I'll give you
接下来
a different scenario for you to practice what you've learned here.
我将布置一个不同的任务 让你有机会练习所学的知识
I find that experimenting and playing with parameters is a great empirical way
我发现实验和调整参数是很好的实践机会
to gain intuition and better understanding of modeling techniques.
可以更直观地掌握建模技巧
So try experimenting with tuning and balancing
请尝试优化和平衡你设计的参数
parameters of your own design to see the effect.
然后看看效果如何